[Professional subtitles are being translated. Will be updated soon]
【专业字幕正在翻译中。很快就会更新]
your offline games
你的离线游戏
What is the content?
内容是什么？
Is it that fun?
有那么好玩吗？
When you say that, you complain.
当你这么说的时候，你就会抱怨。
If you don’t tell, you’ll ask again.
如果你不说，你就会再问。
I'm just worried.
我只是担心。
Why do you look like my mother?
你为什么像我妈妈？
Everyone is an adult.
每个人都是成年人。
if something really happened to me
如果我真的发生了什么事
I can handle it myself
我可以自己处理
You said it yourself.
你自己也说了。
No, you're out this time.
不，这次你出去了。
Aren't you happy?
你不是很高兴吗？
What are you sighing about?
你在叹什么？
Can't speak
不能说话
Is there anything else you can't say?
你还有什么不能说的吗？
Are you sad?
你伤心吗？
That's it.
就是这样。
Can you be sad?
你能伤心吗？
It's not a big deal.
这没什么大不了的。
I
我
your brother
你弟弟
Majestic appearance, handsome and elegant
威严的外观 帅气优雅
Good-looking and smarter than anyone else
长得好看，比谁都聪明
I was abandoned by someone.
我被某人抛弃了。
This is very embarrassing.
这非常尴尬。
when
什么时候
Just now
刚才
live in thailand
住在泰国
How long have you two been together?
你们两个在一起多久了？
At first I thought it was just beginning.
起初我以为一切才刚刚开始。
But it was over before it even started.
但事情还没有开始，就已经结束了。
This is what is called unsuccessful.
这就是所谓的不成功。
I think I was scammed.
我想我被骗了。
What have you lost?
你失去了什么？
trust in the world
对这个世界的信任
Brother, are you drunk?
大哥，你喝醉了吗？
I'm a drinker.
我是一个喝很多酒的人。
This time you go to Thailand.
这次你去泰国。
Want to play games?
要去玩游戏吗？
You are still in love.
你仍然恋爱着。
first time playing game
第一次玩游戏
Then it turned into love.
后来就变成了爱情。
How did you two meet?
你们两个是怎么认识的？
partner
伙伴
gaming partner
游戏伙伴
I'm actually a spy.
我其实是一名间谍。
Don't play with me like this.
你别这样跟我玩。
if i were a spy
假如我是一名间谍
Are you going to arrest me?
你要逮捕我吗？
affim
肯定
I don't know any relatives.
我不认识任何亲戚。
What happened?
究竟发生了什么？
I'm kidding you.
我和你开玩笑。
I'm just playing games
我只是在玩游戏
in game
在游戏里
not really
并不真地
You made it very clear
你说得很清楚
Soon you will be traveling across the country again.
很快你将再次穿越这个国家。
Now you're playing spy again.
现在你又扮演间谍了。
what happened
发生了什么
Special mission, have you heard of it?
特别任务，你听说过吗？
have no idea
不知道
This is a special game world.
这是一个特殊的游戏世界。
on the Internet
在互联网上
Yaoyao and I are
我和瑶瑶是
Get to know each other in that world
在那个世界里彼此相识
Yaoyao
瑶瑶
It's all over.
都结束了。
After saying that, he took away my things.
说完，他就拿走了我的东西。
Then she left
然后她就离开了
leave without saying goodbye
不辞而别
No reason.
没有理由。
Can't contact you anymore
无法再联系了
WeChat phone number
微信电话
I have no one left.
我已经没有人留下了。
So I hear you say that.
所以我听到你这么说。
You two are not close.
你们两个并不亲近。
If not, give up.
如果没有，就放弃。
give up
放弃
Am I such a submissive person?
我是这样一个顺从的人吗？
food for men and women
男性和女性的食物
Human greed is extremely huge.
人类的贪婪是极其巨大的。
Let's talk a little more about this.
让我们再多谈谈这个问题。
In other words, I don’t know people.
也就是说，我不认识人。
Say it louder
说大一点
It’s a feeling of dedication to me
是一种为我奉献的感觉
and betrayal of trust
以及信任的背叛
So, are you still playing games?
那么，你还在玩游戏吗？
I'm in love with you
我和你谈恋爱
What games do you usually discuss with me?
你通常和我讨论什么游戏？
Why do you like today?
为什么你喜欢今天？
Let's talk about games like this.
我们来谈谈这样的游戏。
If you continue to play the game
如果你继续玩游戏
Aren't you two still partners?
你们两个不是还是搭档吗？
that's right.
这是正确的。
but
但
I want to know more.
我想了解更多。
in the real world
在现实世界
What kind of person is she?
她是一个什么样的人？
Weren't you very elegant the way you looked before?
你之前的样子不是很优雅吗？
What's wrong with you today?
你今天怎么了？
possible
可能
Is it because she is different from others?
是因为她和其他人不一样吗？
maybe in her real life
也许在她的现实生活中
Not that pretty.
没那么漂亮。
So I wanted to take a look.
所以我想看看。
how unattractive she is
她是多么缺乏吸引力
look.
看。
Completed
完成的
CCTV for this account
此帐号的央视
Notify me when you are online.
当你在线时，通知我。
Yes
是的
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
Miss
女士
Yaoyao
瑶瑶
The two never got back together.
两人再也没有复合。
really surprised me
真的让我很惊讶
Yaoyao left without saying goodbye.
瑶瑶不辞而别。
Why?
为什么？
have no idea
不知道
I always thought
我一直以为
Yaoyao is probably Ye Wu.
瑶瑶大概就是夜雾吧。
Arranged for Huang Zicheng
给黄子成安排的
Is it the person next to you?
是你旁边的人吗？
Have you checked her out?
你查过她吗？
But there wasn’t much doubt.
但没有太多疑问。
this is the best.
这是最好的。
But it can be an offline player.
但可以是离线玩家。
It's not easy.
这并不容易。
Huang Zicheng’s current situation
黄子成现在的状况
I have no idea.
我不知道。
How dangerous is this game?
这个游戏有多危险？
personal computer
个人电脑
Huang Zicheng logs into the game.
黄子成登录游戏。
I'll take you to see
我带你去看
What does he do in the game?
他在游戏中做什么？
May I come in?
我能进来吗？
Why am I dressed like this?
我为什么穿成这样？
Randomly assign accounts to you
为您随机分配账户
There is nothing to choose from.
没有什么可以选择的。
I'm very happy.
我很开心。
Welcome to Special Mission.
欢迎来到特殊使命。
This is where?
这是哪里？
divide space
划分空间
The game will try.
游戏会尝试。
Find players
寻找球员
real geographical location
真实地理位置
Regardless, the game is there.
无论如何，游戏还是有的。
Offline racing section
线下赛车部分
Games can
游戏可以
Big data shows
大数据表明
Your location is locked.
您的位置已锁定。
Just in Jinhai.
就在金海。
Is there such a big country?
有这么大的国家吗？
this game
这个游戏
aim at the world
瞄准世界
So never be specific.
所以永远不要具体。
someone
有人
Or somewhere?
或者是在某个地方？
If I lived in Zhenhai
如果我住在镇海
Will I receive assignments from Paris?
我会收到来自巴黎的任务吗？
OK
好的
I just want you.
我只是要你。
Points and levels must be accumulated.
积分和等级必须累积。
You can now open another map.
您现在可以打开另一张地图。
Player novice
玩家小白
You must use Xiaobai's equipment.
必须使用小白的装备。
Advanced players can use the skateboard.
高级玩家可以使用滑板。
If you like
如果你喜欢
I can lend it to you.
我可以借给你。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
This is better.
这个比较好。
I don’t know how to skateboard.
我不知道怎么玩滑板。
right here
就在这儿
This is the first level of the game.
是游戏的第一关。
There is only one pass here.
这里只有一个通行证。
in order to be able to enter
为了能够进入
game provinces
游戏省份
So the mission begins.
所以任务开始了。
This is for new players.
这是给新玩家的。
Familiar with all games
熟悉所有游戏
There will be a prompt on the page.
页面会有提示。
You just need to follow the prompts.
您只需按照提示操作即可。
Come and take control of your body.
快来控制你的身体吧。
This is enough.
这就够了。
Players get ready
选手们做好准备
The game is about to begin.
比赛即将开始。
Let's do it again.
让我们再来一次。
over time
随着时间的推移
mission failed
任务失败
What's this?
这是什么？
It looks like the world of this game.
看起来就像是这个游戏的世界。
It's really not suitable for you.
确实不适合你。
Now I'm just not familiar with the operation.
现在我只是不熟悉操作。
I believe this.
我相信这个。
Come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧。
try again
再试一次
do it again.
再来一遍。
It's not that you can't pass this.
并不是说你过不了这一关。
Can't access the main map?
无法访问主地图？
Wait until you pass this level.
等你通过这一关。
Then Huang Zicheng must have been online for a long time.
那黄子成肯定在线很久了。
Let's go, let's go, come on, come on.
走吧，走吧，快点，快点。
You follow me carefully.
你小心翼翼地跟着我。
Please show me the way.
请给我指路。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
When you show up, there's a random mission.
当你出现时，有一个随机任务。
The weather is dry.
天气干燥。
Beware of fire
小心火灾
The show is about to begin.
演出即将开始。
white goat herder
白山羊牧民
The wind blew his hat away.
风把他的帽子吹走了。
Puzzle game
益智游戏
How about a pair of skateboards?
一双滑板怎么样？
I don't want you to do anything.
我不想让你做任何事。
Use your brain a little bit.
你稍微用点脑子。
Do something nice for me
帮我做点好事吧
Come up and get ready.
上来准备开始吧。
Players get ready
选手们做好准备
The game is about to begin.
比赛即将开始。
yield
屈服
Please be careful with it.
请小心。
Kite
风筝
First
第一
1 minute 58 seconds
1分58秒
Astonishing.
惊人的。
affect both
两者都影响
my show
我的节目
This is the coin in the game.
这是游戏中的硬币。
correct
正确的
How to redeem?
如何兑换？
application
应用
Linked international credit cards
关联国际信用卡
direct exchange
直接交换
if you say now
如果你现在说
a coin
一枚硬币
They can be redeemed for about one dollar.
它们可以以大约一美元的价格兑换。
This mission only costs one dollar.
这个任务只要一美元。
So do you know why?
那你知道为什么吗？
Attracting so many gamers.
吸引了如此多的游戏玩家。
There are many gamers.
游戏玩家有很多。
How about your mission?
你的使命怎么样？
Do you have any other clues?
你还有什么线索吗？
one night
一夜
The weather is dry, so pay attention to fire prevention.
天气干燥，注意防火。
It was 7pm.
那是晚上 7 点。
until the age of twenty-one
直到二十一岁
Performance
表现
We just passed by.
我们刚才路过。
theater
剧院
What about electronic screens in theaters?
剧院的电子屏幕怎么样？
Announcement sample
公告样本
It was nineteen o'clock in the evening.
当时是晚上十九点。
until the age of twenty-one
直到二十一岁
white goat herder
白山羊牧民
hat
帽子
That's the one wearing it
就是那个穿的人
man in white hat
戴白帽子的人
in this regard
在这方面
Talent indeed.
确实有才华。
But the coordination of the body
但这身体的协调性
something missing
有点缺失
head office
总公司
This is where?
这是哪里？
behind this door
这扇门后面
This is a real spy world.
这是一个真正的间谍世界。
Take you to see
带你去看
go
去
player kite
玩家风筝
Level 18
18级
go through
经过
It's nothing, just playing games secretly, sir.
没什么，就是偷偷玩游戏而已，先生。
Are the players happy?
玩家们开心吗？
Level 1
1级
go through
经过
This is the mission center.
这是任务中心。
Whether you are a junior player
无论是初级玩家
Or a high-level player
或者高水平的玩家
You have to accept a quest here.
你必须在这里接受一个任务。
Improve the level of
提高水平
There
那里
This is a mission where you have to pick up the newspaper.
这是一个你必须拿起报纸的任务。
you can stay here
你可以留在这里
according to your level
根据你的水平
Select all
选择所有内容
The mission you want to do
你想做的使命
Performance example
性能示例
Nineteen to twenty-one years old
十九岁到二十一岁
Some stories about country M and country I
关于M国和I国的一些故事
You are here.
你在这。
your mission
你的使命
Who will you find?
你会找到谁？
shepherd
牧羊人
Send the letter to the counter of the head office.
寄信到总公司柜台。
Someone is waiting for you.
有人在等你。
Congratulations on completing your mission.
恭喜你完成任务。
Rich again
又有钱了
It's too easy.
这太容易了。
You are very professional
你很专业
Ordinary player
普通玩家
It's not that easy anymore.
这不再那么容易了。
If you hadn't taken me away
如果不是你带我走
I can't come in.
我不能进来。
Good to know.
很高兴知道。
Quests for novice players
适合新手玩家的任务
They're all playing a little bit.
他们都在玩一点。
by upgrading
通过升级
The difficulty level of their tasks
他们的任务的难度级别
will increase
将增加
and the awards they received
以及他们获得的奖项
if i want to change money
如果我想换钱
Do I have to link my bank card?
我必须关联我的银行卡吗？
credit card
信用卡
Why
为什么
Did you guess it?
你猜到了？
related to punitive measures
与惩罚措施有关
You are considered smart.
你被认为很聪明。
Games allow players to make money.
游戏可以让玩家赚钱。
Can find ways to intimidate players.
能想办法恐吓玩家。
especially those
尤其是那些
Spy chosen player
间谍选择的玩家
If the player wants to give up midway
如果玩家想中途放弃
Then the game will be broken.
那么游戏就会被打破。
Credit card amount
信用卡金额
threaten
威胁
Force them not to give up easily
迫使他们不轻易放弃
very careful
非常小心
There's a lot more going on here.
这里还有很多事情。
Online tasks
在线任务
Unravel the mystery of the secret room
解开密室之谜
gun shooting position
枪射击位置
Cool, adventurous run
酷炫、冒险的奔跑
killing game
杀人游戏
There's even Border Week.
甚至还有博德周。
They are covered.
他们被覆盖了。
Inside the shell of the spy world
在间谍世界的外壳里
let those dreams be
让那些梦想成为
007 actors
007的演员们
You can stay here.
你可以留在这里。
move
感动
spy life
间谍生活
There is an incense car here.
这里有一辆香车。
beautiful wine
漂亮的酒
beautiful people
漂亮的人
Information about the international situation
有关国际局势的信息
Life
生活
life in bullet forest
子弹森林的生活
also,
此外，
they are ok
他们还可以
Continue to fulfill our mission
持续履行使命
to earn coins
来赚取金币
But their goal
但他们的目标
Just one thing.
只有一件事。
Become a legendary elite officer
成为传奇的精英军官
Accept offline competitions
接受线下比赛
but they don't know
但他们不知道
when they come into contact
当他们接触时
Offline challenge
线下挑战
Neither will they.
他们也不会。
Lucky again in my own eyes
我自己眼中再次幸运
you are looking for
你正在寻找
these famous spies
这些著名的间谍
Yes
是的
they are
他们是
Player dragged into water
被拖入水中的玩家
Huang Zicheng may be
黄子成可能是
next spy
下一个间谍
So we need him.
所以我们需要他。
Huang Zicheng was also present.
黄子成也在场。
Is he really that handsome?
他真的有那么帅吗？
Sir, would you like something to drink?
先生，您想喝点什么吗？
I'm waiting for someone.
我在等一个人。
Yes
是的
This is the mission of an agent.
这就是特工的使命。
Game trading platform
游戏交易平台
here
这里
There is no information that money cannot buy.
没有金钱买不到的信息。
Is it just in-game?
只是游戏中的情况吗？
of course not.
当然不。
special mission
特殊使命
Not just
不只是
This is a simple game.
这是一个简单的游戏。
Many effects will be used.
将使用许多影响。
The secret of this game
这个游戏的秘密
carry out information exchange
开展信息交流
Even if this game
就算这个游戏
Cut down on offline tasks
削减离线任务
Online game platform
网络游戏平台
It's not that pure.
并不是那么纯粹。
so
所以
Here is equal to
这里等于
secret information exchange point
秘密信息交换点
Yes
是的
Huang Zicheng must be looking for it.
黄子成一定是在寻找。
Definitely information about Yaoyao.
绝对是关于瑶瑶的信息。
mourn
哀悼
This one is for you.
这个是给你的。
Is that Yaoyao?
那是瑶瑶吗？
That's not it.
不是这个。
Yaoyao's account is Anna.
瑶瑶的账号叫安娜。
Anna
安娜
Gaoke
高克
hospital news
医院新闻
Yu Xiaoyue has recovered.
玉小月已经康复了。
go
去
Give me such good equipment.
给我这么好的装备。
It seems that online games have made a lot of money.
看来网络游戏已经赚了不少钱了。
Already have money
已经有钱了
Of course I won't forget you.
我当然不会忘记你。
happy together
一起高兴
Your happiness needs to be exchanged.
你的幸福是需要交换的。
Please speak up.
请说出来。
Why do you ask me?
你为什么要求我？
You are still the one who understands me.
你依然是那个懂我的人。
Get out your devil claws.
拿出你的恶魔爪子。
Can you help me find a player?
你能帮我找一个球员吗？
Nickname is Anna
昵称是安娜
Miss
女士
What's wrong with you two?
你们两个怎么了？
be a partner
是一个合作伙伴
Partners who perform offline tasks
执行离线任务的伙伴
Do I still need to find it?
还需要我去找吗？
I was in a hurry when I went there.
我去的时候太匆忙了。
There is no contact number.
没有联系电话。
Do you want to flirt with him?
你要和他调情吗？
No
不
I need to check on her.
我需要检查一下她。
what's wrong with you?
你这人怎么回事？
Very suspicious
非常可疑
keep leaving me
继续离开我
I was lied to.
我被骗了。
I have to get my face back.
我必须拿回我的脸。
Your dignity is something you find yourself.
你的尊严是你自己寻找的。
Aren't you my glory?
你不是我的荣耀吗？
Get over it.
克服它。
I'm still worried that you can't find me.
我还是担心你找不到我。
Is there anyone I can't find?
有我找不到的人吗？
Name: Yao Yao
姓名：姚姚
Nickname Anna
昵称安娜
Level 38
38级
Gimhae City female athletes
金海市女选手
It's already started.
已经开始了。
Offline mission mode
离线任务模式
Beautiful?
美丽吗？
No, does this have anything to do with finding someone?
不是，这和找人有什么关系吗？
No
没有
I just want to know.
我只是想知道。
Do you have a solution?
你有解决方案吗？
I can help you find it.
我可以帮你找到它。
can be compensated
可以得到补偿
How many
多少
two thousand gold coins
两千金币
Did I hear that correctly?
我没听错吧？
Find a man and get fifty percent off.
找个男人可以享受百分之五十的折扣。
No. Are you considerate enough?
不，你够体贴吗？
Can you find it?
你能找到吗？
Look for
寻找
Please wait for news.
请等待消息。
A really old-fashioned name
确实很老气的名字
There are already too many players named Anna.
叫安娜的玩家已经太多了。
There are many players named Anna.
有很多叫安娜的球员。
There are only 6 people in the Chinese area.
华人区只有6个人。
That's the highest level of people.
那是最高级别的人。
That level 38
那个38级
There is no level 38.
没有38级。
You always brag to me
你老是向我吹牛
There are level 42 people.
有42级的人。
What?
什么？
This is high
这个高
She may be worried that you will be disappointed.
她可能担心你会失望。
So he hid his abilities.
所以他隐藏了自己的能力。
empowered women like us
像我们这样有能力的女性
Everyone will consider it
各人都会考虑
man's feelings
男人的感受
Then it's probably him.
那么很可能就是他了。
Jin Hai didn’t.
金海没有。
There is no better player than this.
没有比这更好的球员了。
But there is little information about her game.
但有关她比赛的信息却很少。
I sent the relevant social accounts
我发送了相关社交账号
send to you
寄给你
try it yourself.
你试试看。
It's up to you whether you can find it or not.
能不能找到就看你自己了。
OK
好的
You send it to me.
你把它发给我。
A picture is enough.
有图就够了。
You probably won't use this image.
你可能不会使用这张图片。
But you have to exchange photos to find people, right?
但你必须交换照片才能找到人，对吗？
photographic equipment
摄影器材
filming time
拍摄时间
And the economic level of shooting
以及拍摄的经济水平
present in all messages
存在于所有消息中
If your photo
如果你的照片
You downloaded it empty handed.
你空手下载了它。
Let me take a look at this phone model
我看看这个手​​机型号
just like hers
就像她的一样
Another point is the time of this shooting.
还有一点就是这次拍摄的时间。
That was last month.
那是上个月的事了。
She should have taken the photo, right?
应该是她拍的吧？
flirt with girls
和女孩调情
The effort really went into it.
确实付出了努力。
Yes
是的
Desire is control
欲望就是控制
The driving force behind technological progress
技术进步的原动力
Already placed.
已经放置了。
It should be you.
应该是你。
if i tell you now
如果我现在告诉你
Does this count as surrender?
这算不算投降？
It depends on your attitude.
这取决于你的态度。
The B13 example was taken by myself.
B13的例子是我自己拿的。
Who gave you the order?
谁给你下的命令？
professor
教授
Who is the professor?
教授到底是谁？
He said he was Professor Li.
他说他是李教授。
Australian Chinese professor
澳大利亚华人教授
Have you seen it?
你见过吗？
no way
绝不
We keep in touch online.
我们在网上保持联系。
So how did you meet?
那么你们是怎么认识的呢？
I sent the application
我发送了申请
Application submitted
已提交申请
The school then responded to my email.
之后学校就回复了我的邮件。
He was the one who contacted me.
联系我的人就是他。
He said he saw my message.
他说他看到了我的信息。
admire me very much
非常佩服我
But I applied to this school.
但我申请了这所学校。
Must be a leading international magazine
必须是领先的国际杂志
Published papers
发表论文
The magazine I am publishing now
我现在出版的杂志
no rights
无权利
He said he could help me.
他说他可以帮助我。
But the condition is
但条件是
in my paper
在我的论文中
The latest experimental data must be available.
必须有最新的实验数据。
Experimental data support
实验数据支持
He gave me encouragement.
他给了我鼓励。
Steal organizational information
窃取机构信息
I thought then
那时我想
Can apply
可以申请
I thought I'd use a little information.
我想我会使用一点信息。
There should be nothing.
应该没有什么。
I've already done this.
我已经这么做了。
unimaginable
难以想象
My nightmare begins.
我的噩梦开始了。
Your paper is very good.
你的论文非常好。
lecturer
讲师
So my request
所以我的要求
Have you passed?
你已经通过了吗？
affim
肯定
But there's another thing.
但还有另外一件事。
it has to be done by you
这必须由你来完成
about what?
关于什么？
I think
我想
Latest research reports
最新研究报告
of your laboratory
你的实验室的
Are you kidding me?
你开什么玩笑？
It was a document related to secrets.
那是一份与秘密有关的文件。
What are you afraid of?
你怕什么呢？
This is not the first time.
这已经不是第一次了。
Later I deleted it
后来我删除了
his contact channels
他的联系渠道
But I can't get rid of it.
但我无法摆脱它。
He started using various methods.
他开始使用各种方法。
appear in my life
出现在我的生活中
threaten me
威胁我
That’s enough for today’s live broadcast.
今天的直播就够了。
thank you all
谢谢大家
You have given up.
你已经放弃了。
I'm worried he will
我担心他会
Publish my paper and steal information
发表我的论文，窃取信息
Just like that, I'm done.
就这样，我就完成了。
So you just go and get it.
所以你就去得到了。
I'm the one managing this report.
我是负责管理这份报告的人。
so easy
好简单
How do they know?
他们怎么知道？
You will see the test report.
您将看到试验报告。
Because I applied
因为我申请了
in personal history of school
在学校的个人历史中
It says I work at the institute.
上面写着我在该研究所工作。
Daily updated report
每日更新报告
Have you ever disclosed it?
你曾经透露过吗？
I've never had this
这个我从来没有
why do you believe
你为什么相信
The Australian professor
这位澳大利亚教授
At that time I received
当时我收到
From a real Australian school
来自真正的澳大利亚学校
this is not about
这不是关于
This has nothing to do with you.
这与你无关。
He's just using it.
他只是在使用它。
Australian professor status
澳大利亚教授身份
Let's hide ourselves.
我们把自己隐藏起来吧。
Say something.
说一点。
Steps you take to steal a sample
您窃取样本的步骤
sample container
样品容器
Where did it come from?
它从哪里来的？
that
那个
The professor sent it to me.
教授发给我的。
He also designed the battle plan.
作战计划也是他设计的。
I will take samples.
我会取样。
Paths issued by the Institute
研究所发出的路径
It was all designed by him.
这一切都是他设计的。
he understands
他明白
Do you understand a lot?
你明白很多了吗？
sometimes i feel
有时我觉得
he is beside me
他就在我身边
He is the person beside you.
他就是你身边的人。
But I noticed.
但我注意到了。
The colleague next to me
我旁边的同事
nothing found
什么也没找到
Where is Chu Lei?
楚雷呢？
I guess that's not him.
我想那不是他。
He knew she was going to study abroad.
他知道她要出国留学。
He also knows you will
他也知道你会
It's also in the magazine
杂志上也有
Yes
是的
But this is a matter of going abroad.
但这是出国的事情。
He always disagreed.
他一直不同意。
in this matter
在这件事上
We are two different people.
我们两个人不一样。
About studying abroad
关于出国留学
related business
相关事宜
I almost never tell him.
我几乎从来不告诉他。
Moreover, he has always been very kind to me.
而且，他一直对我很好。
I don't believe he would hurt me.
我不相信他会伤害我。
you don't like
你不喜欢
I've been a fan of this for a long time.
我已经是这个粉丝很长时间了。
Really?
真的吗？
I have no idea
我不知道
People's hearts can change.
人的心可能会改变。
But when I was most helpless
但在我最无助的时候
They are all around me.
我身边的他们都是他。
protect me
保护我
continue to be my friend
继续当我的朋友
He also asked me to surrender.
他还让我投降。
australian school
澳大利亚学校
absolutely not.
根本没有。
This Professor Li
这位李教授
All the information he gave Yu Xiaoyue
他给于小月的所有信息
all fake.
都是假的。
Anyone curious?
有人好奇吗？
sir ray
雷爵士
But the evidence is now insufficient.
但现在证据不足。
But there is one thing.
但有一件事。
I still can't figure it out.
我还是想不通。
Now it seems
现在看来
He still loves Xiao Yue very much.
他还是很爱萧月的。
when i love you
当我爱你的时候
Why drag her into the water?
为什么要把她拖到水里？
love can change
爱可以改变
Love can be expressed
爱是可以表达的
This is because we only know
这是因为我们只知道
Goals like Shre Lei
像Shre Lei这样的目标
So there are a lot of doubts.
所以有很多疑点。
will be close to him
会接近他
Colleagues in Yu Xiaoyue's laboratory
于晓月实验室同事
It's all possible.
这一切都有可能。
Although Chu Lei is the most suspicious.
虽然楚雷是最可疑的。
So he must be a professor, right?
那么他一定是一名教授，对吧？
or that
或者那个
There is another person behind him.
他的身后还有另一个人。
I think Liu’s analysis
我觉得大刘的分析
will be more neutral
会更加中立
Able to monitor Chu Lei
能够监视楚雷
but
但
You can't keep an eye on him alone.
不能一个人盯着他。
For those associated with their laboratories
对于与其实验室相关的人员
Go to watch list
进入观察列表
I have to accept it.
我必须接受它。
Others around Yu Xiaoyue
于小月身边的其他人
check it out.
一探究竟。
Also, how is Han Jie doing?
还有，韩洁那边怎么样了？
nothing happened
什么都没发生
He is moving now.
他现在要搬家了。
Stay in the store temporarily
暂时住在店里
my quote
我的报价
Let’s wait until he stabilizes first.
先等他稳定下来再说。
Let's take action.
让我们采取行动吧。
able
能
Hangyul is just transportation.
Hangyul只是交通。
He's not really a secret thief.
他并不是真正的秘密窃贼。
There is no need to touch him.
没有必要碰他。
But you have to stick to the line.
但你必须坚持这条线。
must fight for us
必须为我们而战
Give us more time and clues.
给我们更多的时间和线索。
Find the people behind the scenes.
找到隐藏在幕后的人。
excellent staff
优秀的员工
I see.
我明白。
OK
好的
Are you two together?
你们两个在一起吗？
I have a seminar next week.
下周我有一个研讨会。
Please help me prepare it.
请帮我准备一下。
Meeting information
会议信息
What seminar?
什么研讨会？
like this.
就像这样。
I have an old friend.
我有一个老朋友。
He is an expert in biology.
他是一位生物学专家。
First I will go to Beijing.
首先我会去北京。
I asked him to come to our Jinhai first.
我让他先来我们金海。
Please consult an academic first.
请先咨询学者。
He is an international expert.
他是一位国际专家。
Become an international expert
成为国际专家
Invitations are not easy.
邀请并不容易。
Yes, I understand.
是的我明白。
meeting schedule
会议时间表
I've sent it to your email.
我已将其发送到您的电子邮件中。
this time
这次
You two are in charge of reception.
你们两个负责接待。
The original intention of reading philosophy
读哲学的初衷
Just bring knowledge
就是带来知识
to the chinese people
对中国人民
How is the reform carried out?
改革是如何进行的？
as
作为
Professional knowledge Q&A website
专业知识问答网站
Read our philosophy
阅读我们的理念
I'm working hard.
我正在努力工作。
Gather quality customers
聚集优质客户
Produce professional content
制作专业内容
To everyone who comes into contact with philosophy
致每一个接触哲学的人
You will get an authoritative answer.
将会得到权威的答复。
How was your time this time?
这次玩得怎么样？
This is enough.
这就够了。
Have you met anyone?
你见过任何人吗？
Interesting person
有趣的人
have
有
after that
在那之后
Let's hang out together.
我们一起出去玩吧。
break up
拆散
No intention and no virtue
无心无德
Live a hundred years
活一百岁
well done
做得好
Open a new bar
开一家新酒吧
Would you like to play with me?
你愿意和我一起去玩吗？
I'd rather not go.
我宁愿不去。
I need a break.
我需要休息一下。
So I'm leaving.
所以我要走了。
you go.
你去。
goodbye
再见
Why leave without saying goodbye?
为何不辞而别？
Game over.
游戏结束了。
And then it's over.
然后就结束了。
Can't we be together?
我们就不能在一起吗？
Games and reality are two different worlds.
游戏和现实是两个不同的世界。
Is it necessary to separate them so far?
有必要把他们分开那么远吗？
Don't want to create problems.
不想制造问题。
I am your problem.
我就是你的问题。
possible
可能的
The first stage has a total of five thousand gold coins.
第一阶段一共五千金币。
We are two and a half
我们两个半
to find you
为了找到你
I've almost used them all.
我已经快全部用完了。
You don't have to do this.
你不必这样做。
but i can't control myself
但我无法控制自己
It sounds like you do have a problem.
听起来你确实是个问题。
What
什么
You said I was a problem, didn't you?
你说我是一个问题，不是吗？
now i tell you
现在我告诉你
Your problem really comes.
你的问题真的来了。
What does it mean?
意味着什么？
take you to a place
带你去一个地方
I dont go.
我不去。
It's not up to you.
这不取决于你。
All wet.
都湿了。
very comfortable
非常舒服
This is the first time I know Jin Hai
我还是第一次知道金海
There are still such clean beaches.
还是有这么干净的海滩。
Why are you
你为什么
It's like I've never seen anything.
就好像我什么都没见过一样。
grew up in china
在中国长大
Los Angeles
洛杉矶
Los Angeles has the ocean.
洛杉矶有海。
only
只是
The chances are slim.
机会很小。
Just have fun and play.
就开心地玩吧。
So what did you do?
那么你做了些什么？
hardworking
勤奋学习
No
不
trying to make money
试图赚钱
You may not tell the story of your childhood.
你可能不会讲述你童年的故事。
Please listen to me, okay?
请听我说，好吗？
Who told you to make money?
谁告诉你要赚钱的？
Definitely not happy.
肯定不会高兴。
you prepare
你准备
Have you given it to me already?
你已经给我了吗？
everything is a surprise
一切都是惊喜
Let's go eat seafood
我们去吃海鲜吧
seafood?
海鲜？
Please take your time.
请慢慢来。
It's really nice here.
这里确实不错。
How did you find it?
你是怎样找到它的？
this is my friend
这是我的朋友
You saw my face and ate it.
你看到了我的脸并吃了它。
The store is not allowed to be open to outsiders.
店铺不准对外人开放。
You have a great face.
你有一张很棒的脸。
Definitely already
肯定已经
I grew up in Little South Bay.
我在小南湾区长大。
Known as the King of the South Bay Area.
被称为南湾区王。
Who doesn’t grow hair?
谁不留头发呢？
Then
然后
From now on, I still have to rely on you to protect me.
从现在开始，我还是要靠你来保护我。
I met you in real life
我在现实生活中遇见了你
Not quite like in the game
不太像游戏中的样子
that game
那场比赛
this is another world
这是另一个世界
so you think
所以你认为
Is this all a lie in the game?
难道这一切都是游戏里的谎言吗？
No
不
At least the prize is real.
至少奖金是真实的。
Why did you come to Jinhai?
你为什么来金海？
I don’t want to live in Los Angeles.
我不想住在洛杉矶。
has a problem.
有问题。
Yes
是的
No wonder he left without saying goodbye.
难怪他不辞而别。
It seems that the previous lessons have been learned.
看来之前的教训已经得到了。
Come on, what does it look like? let me see.
来吧，它看起来像什么？让我看看。
Why are you gossiping like this?
你为什么要这样八卦呢？
I just want to see if I'm handsome or not
我就是想看看自己帅不帅
Are you handsomer than me?
你比我帅吗？
No
没有
of course not.
当然不。
I'm still young and don't know.
我还年轻，不知道。
already
早在
I don't have you yet
我还没有你呢
on a handsome man
在一个英俊的男人身上
wasted many years
浪费了很多年的时间
Your words have been heard.
你的话已经被听到了。
Why is it so uncomfortable?
为什么这么不舒服？
alright.
好啦好啦。
drink alcoholic beverages
喝含酒精饮料
We were friends from college.
我们是大学时代的朋友。
We have been together for four years.
我们已经在一起四年了。
On graduation day, he suddenly told me,
毕业那天，他突然告诉我，
His father was very ill.
他的父亲病得很重。
This requires a lot of money.
这需要很多钱。
this disease
这种病
like a bottomless hole
就像一个没有底的洞
Gonna dig us both out until we're gone.
要把我们两个挖出来，直到我们消失为止。
Another thing about him
他的另一件事
No money.
没有钱。
The study abroad loan has not been paid off.
出国留学贷款没有还清。
So he said to me
于是他对我说
Let me no longer be a burden
让我不再成为负担
You must break up with me.
你必须和我分手。
Who would believe these words?
谁会相信这些话？
Who believes it and who is stupid?
谁信谁傻？
I believe this.
我相信这个。
I not only believe
我不仅相信
I still feel so guilty.
我仍然感到很内疚。
I thought then
那时我想
cannot
不能
I have to face him.
我必须面对他。
if you like someone
如果你喜欢一个人
You should stay with him.
你应该留在他身边。
face everything
面对一切
correct?
正确的？
So I went home.
于是我回家了。
Take all your savings
拿走所有积蓄
I'll go find him
我去找他
after that?
在那之后？
You just don't know.
你只是不知道。
The grandson is in the hotel.
那个孙子在旅馆里。
Arrange a wedding with someone else
与别人安排婚礼
Talk about the bride
说新娘
Both rich and powerful
既有钱又有势
But his face is a bit ugly.
不过脸色有点难看。
What about his father?
那么他的父亲呢？
His father was even more unbelievable.
他的父亲更是难以置信。
at a party
在一次聚会
This is what is called great happiness.
这就是所谓的非常幸福。
The old man is a martial artist.
这位老人是一名武术家。
A man flipped onto the stage.
一个人翻转到了舞台上。
Throw a set of punches.
打出一组拳。
This guy is too funny.
这家伙也太搞笑了吧。
I'm a boxer myself.
我自己也是一名拳击手。
But my father's body
但父亲的尸体
very good
非常好
looks charming
看起来很迷人
majesty
威严
Nothing at all.
什么都没有。
Actually I understand him very well.
其实我很理解他。
are you alone?
你一个人吗？
Living abroad is not easy.
在国外生活并不容易。
Who doesn’t want to work hard for ten less years?
谁不想少奋斗十年呢？
correct?
正确的？
so
所以
So you are angry.
所以你生气了。
Return to Gimhae
返回金海
I received it accidentally
我无意中收到了
Prajna Acceptance Notice
般若录用通知书
Want to change the environment
想换个环境
So here I am.
所以我来了。
So you're here to treat the wound?
所以你是来治疗伤口的？
Am I really that weak?
我真的有那么弱吗？
And one more thing
还有一件事
if it weren't for him
如果不是他
Can we two have grilled fish here?
我们两个可以在这里吃烤鱼吗？
Yeah
对对对
you
你
Normally he seems smart.
平时他看起来很聪明。
Why is timing important?
为什么时机很重要？
How stupid is this?
这有多愚蠢？
When others hear it, they think it is a lie.
别人一听，就觉得是骗人的。
Can you still believe it?
你还能相信吗？
Now that I think about it, it's really ridiculous.
现在想来，真是可笑。
but our people
但我们的人民
stuck in feeling
陷入感觉
when there
当在那里的时候
Must be blind
一定是瞎子
But it's really stupid.
但这确实很愚蠢。
What's your job?
你做什么工作？
How do you comfort her?
你怎么安慰她？
Your hands are covered in oil.
你的手沾满了油。
Don't touch my head.
别碰我的头。
I don't need comfort.
我不需要安慰。
Nothing happened, fine.
没什么事，很好。
Then you shouldn't because
那么你不应该因为
I once met a bad guy.
我曾经遇到过一个坏人。
Let us deny all this.
让我们否认这一切吧。
This isn't fair.
这不公平。
Sometimes I wonder.
有时我会想。
Very, very strange indeed.
确实非常非常奇怪。
Some people have been together for that long.
有些人已经在一起那么久了。
I think I know better.
我想我更了解。
But in the end you find
但最后你发现
What is the other person thinking?
对方到底在想什么？
I am oblivious.
你什么都不知道。
i allow you
我允许你
Can test me over and over again
可以一遍又一遍地考验我
Are you that confident?
你有那么自信吗？
if this makes you
如果这让你
It gives people a sense of security.
它给人一种安全感。
I'm OK
我没问题
from the first time
从第一次
first time see me
第一次见到我
it's my personality
是我的个性
You can easily get hurt this way.
这样你很容易受伤。
compared to injury
与受伤相比
I'm more afraid of missing out.
我更害怕错过。
You have received the assignment.
你已经接到任务了。
Such a high bonus
这么高的奖金
The higher the bonus
奖金越高
This means the risk is higher.
这意味着风险更高。
I can only talk about this mission.
我只能谈谈这个任务。
more dangerous than before
比以前更危险
received
已收到
will you come?
你会来吗？
affim
肯定
I can
我会
How can you go alone?
你怎么能一个人去呢？